If you want someone to do something and they're not doing it,
you have like four or five reasons that they're not doing it.
The first is they just didn't know that you wanted them to do it. Most common.
Hey, did you do that thing? And they're like, what thing? You're like, damn it.
I didn't write it down. Did I? So now I say, why didn't you do that thing? They
say, well, I didn't know how to do it. Okay. Now let's say we train them.
So I told you that you needed to do it. You know how to do it,
but you didn't know when, oh, I need to do that tomorrow.
The next is you have something that's blocking you. So I knew that I knew how,
I knew you wanted to do it tomorrow, but you also told me to do three other things.
Which one did you want me to do? Finally, you get into this,
which is that I didn't want to do it,
which in my experience is the first place that we go to as entrepreneurs.
And typically the last one that's reality.
Most people I have found when they have a job prefer to keep it.
And I've also found that most people prefer to feel like they're doing a good
job at their job. It's usually one of these other issues.